<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>QSocket</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on QSocket</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>The Quantum Socket Toolkit allows two system behind NAT/Firewall to establish a TCP/TLS connection with each other.
The qsocket library locally derives a universally unique identifier (UUID) and connects two devices through the Quantum Socket Relay Network (QSRN) regardless and independent of the network layers, local IP Address or geographical location. The entire qsocket project is ported from the original gsocket toolkit of THC.
But Why? So why did you reinvent the wheel?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/changelog/</guid>
      <description>Changelog v1.0.1 (2022/04/02) Fixed Fix img style issue, it should be max-width instead of width (#10) v1.0.0 - First Major Release (2022/04/01) Added Layout New Layout: Postcard Layout, Blank Layout Support pagination for Postcard Layout and List Layout Enhance list layout date format. If current list layout is grouped by year, hide list item&amp;rsquo;s year. Redesign default home page layout using Postcard Layout Add sidebar for better navbar responsiveness on small screen New Shortcode emgithub: directly embed github source code like gist with Prism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Examples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/examples/</guid>
      <description>Examples RDP connection over QSRN ADB access over QSRN Usage:
SSH from Workstation B to Workstation A through any firewall/NAT $ qs-netcat -f &amp;quot;localhost:22&amp;quot; -l # Workstation A $ qsocket ssh root@qsocket # Workstation B Log in to Workstation A from Workstation B through any firewall/NAT $ qs-netcat -l -i # Workstation A $ qs-netcat -i # Workstation B Transfer files from Workstation B to Workstation A $ qs-netcat -q -s MySecret -l &amp;gt; file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QSocket Relay Network</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/qsrn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/qsrn/</guid>
      <description>The relay server is the back bone of the QSocket project. It is designed for relaying the incoming QSocket connections with high performance and scalability. The official relay instance for the QSocket project gate.qsocket.io is available for public use totally free of charge. But we advise everyone to setup their own relays on their own infrastructure.
Benchmarks A single qsr instance with a 2GB RAM and 1 CPU cores can handle between 30.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>